uh sir i want to ask about individual
insurance which type of insurance we
should i should take because i am
running a dedicated center in
ophthalmology
okay there are two two types of
individuals
with indian medical association and
another is all the insurance companies
okay right you can you should actually
ideally have both of them
i should take both four but
okay
they can be uh they can be utilized as
simultaneously for a big cover
sir i heard about two types
okay so you can take that a little bit
of 5000 extra for insurance and include
the advocate fees also in the insurance
so you take both of them and um like one
one if you have one crn
from imc one cr from icic in case of two
cr claim they can be club also
not imcm
hello sir
sorry sorry i am a indian medical
assistant yeah okay sir i am
thank you sir